Finding aid for the Hearst Corporation Los Angeles Examiner photographs, negatives and clippings - oversize portrait and subject files 7000.3
USC Libraries Special Collections
- Oversize Portrait Files
  - T, U, V
    - Tregoff, Carole (Box 191, Folder 12)
    - Tregoff, Gladys (Box 191, Folder 13)
    - Trent -- Miscellaneous (Box 191, Folder 14)
    - Trevor, Claire -- Actress (Box 194, Folder 1)
    - Trippi, Charlie -- Football (Box 194, Folder 2)
    - Troubetskoy -- Miscellaneous (Box 194, Folder 3)
    - Truman -- Miscellaneous (Box 195, Folder 1)
    - Truman, Harry -- Former President (Box 195, Folder 2)
    - Truman, Harry S. -- All Pictures Without Him (Box 195, Folder 10)
    - Truman, Harry S. -- Mrs. (Box 195, Folder 12)
    - Truman, Harry, President -- Alone (Box 196, Folder 4)
    - Truman, Harry, President -- Assassination Attempt November 1, 1950 (Box 196, Folder 1)
    - Truman, Harry, President -- Citizen - January 1953 (Box 196, Folder 3)
    - Truman, Harry, President -- Inauguration (Box 196, Folder 2)
    - Truman, Harry, President -- With Family (Box 196, Folder 5)
    - Truman, Margaret (Box 196, Folder 6)
    - Truman, President -- Heads (Box 195, Folder 3)
    - Truman, President -- Speaking (Box 195, Folder 4-9)
    - Truman, President -- With Manuel Aleman (Box 195, Folder 11)
    - Trumbo, Dalton -- Writer (Box 194, Folder 4)
    - Tsa-Tz (Box 194, Folder 5)
    - Tsung-Jen, Li (Box 193, Folder 9)
    - Tucker -- Miscellaneous (Box 193, Folder 10)
    - Tucker, Forrest (Box 193, Folder 11)
    - Tucker, Sophie -- Actress (Box 193, Folder 12)
    - Tufts, Sonny -- Actor (Box 193, Folder 13)
    - Tum Suden, Dickie -- Lost boy (Box 193, Folder 14)
    - Tum Suden, Joseph -- Mr. and Mrs. -- Parents of Lost Boy (Box 193, Folder 15)
    - Turner -- Miscellaneous (Box 193, Folder 16)
    - Turner, Lana -- Alone (Box 193, Folder 1)
    - Turner, Lana -- Groups (Box 193, Folder 2 - 6)
    - Turner, Lana -- Stompanato Case Pictures Only (Box 193, Folder 7 - 8)
    - Turpin, Randy (Box 194, Folder 6)
    - Twelvetrees, Helen -- Actress (Box 194, Folder 7)
    - Tydings, Millard (Box 194, Folder 8)
    - Tyler -- Miscellaneous (Box 194, Folder 9)
    - Tyler, Beverly (Box 194, Folder 10)
    - Tze-Tung, Mao (Box 194, Folder 11)
    - Ua-Uz (Box 196, Folder 7)
    - Va-Vaz (Box 198, Folder 1)
    - Val-Vam (Box 198, Folder 2)
    - Valentine -- Miscellaneous (Box 198, Folder 4)
    - Valentine, Nancy (Box 198, Folder 5)
    - Valentino, Pat (Box 198, Folder 6)
    - Vallee -- Miscellaneous (Box 198, Folder 7)
    - Valli, Virginia (Box 198, Folder 8)
    - Van Alstine, Anthony (Box 198, Folder 10)
    - Van Cleve, Patricia (Box 197, Folder 9)
    - Van Doren, Mamie -- Actress (Box 197, Folder 6)
    - Van Fleet, James A., General (Box 197, Folder 7)
    - Van Horn -- Miscellaneous (Box 197, Folder 10)
    - Van-Vanbe (Box 198, Folder 9)
    - Vanbo-Vanc (Box 198, Folder 11)
    - Vand- (Box 198, Folder 12)
    - Vandenberg -- Miscellaneous (Box 197, Folder 1)
    - Vandenberg, Hoyt S. (Box 197, Folder 3)
    - Vanderberg, Arthur, Senator (Box 197, Folder 2)
    - Vanderbilt -- Miscellaneous (Box 197, Folder 4)
    - Vandergrift -- Miscellaneous (Box 197, Folder 5)
    - Vane-Vanhoof (Box 198, Folder 13)
    - Vanhook-Vank (Box 198, Folder 14)
    - Vanl-Vans (Box 198, Folder 15)
    - Vanw-Vanz (Box 198, Folder 16)
    - Vao-Vaz (Box 198, Folder 3)
    - Vaughan, Harry, Major General (Box 197, Folder 8)
    - Vaughn -- Miscellaneous (Box 197, Folder 11)
    - Ve-Viz (Box 199, Folder 1-9)
    - Veeck, Bill (Box 199, Folder 11)
    - Velde, Harold H. Rep. (Box 199, Folder 12)
    - Velez and Yolanda (Box 199, Folder 13)
    - Velez, Lupe -- Actress (Box 197, Folder 12)
    - Venable, Evelyn -- Actress (Box 197, Folder 13)
    - Venta, Krishna -- Cult leader (Box 197, Folder 15)
    - Venuta, Benay -- Singer (Box 197, Folder 14)
    - Vera, Ellen -- Actress (Box 199, Folder 14)
    - Verdeur, Joe -- Swimmer (Box 199, Folder 15)
    - Vickers, Martha (Box 199, Folder 16)
    - Vidor -- Miscellaneous (Box 199, Folder 17)
    - Vines, Ellsworth -- Golfer (Box 200, Folder 1)
    - Vingo -- Miscellaneous (Box 200, Folder 2)
    - Vinson -- Miscellaneous (Box 200, Folder 3)
    - Vinson, Carl -- Representative of Georgia (Box 200, Folder 4)
    - Vinson, Fred M. (Box 200, Folder 5)
    - Vishinsky, Andrei Y. (Box 200, Folder 6)
    - Vj-Vz (Box 199, Folder 10)
    - Vogeler, Robert A. -- And Wife (Box 200, Folder 7)
    - Von Papen, Franz -- Nazi (Box 200, Folder 12)
    - Von, A-Z (Box 200, Folder 8-11)
  - W
    - Waddington, Dorothy -- Mrs. (Box 201, Folder 1)
    - Wade-Wallace (Box 201, Folder 10-14)
    - Wadleigh, Henry Julian (Box 201, Folder 2)
    - Wadsworth -- Miscellaneous (Box 201, Folder 3)
    - Wagner -- Miscellaneous (Box 201, Folder 4)
    - Wagner, Robert (Box 201, Folder 5)
    - Wainwright, Jonathan, General (Box 201, Folder 6)
    - Waitkus, Eddie (Box 201, Folder 7)
    - Wal-War (Box 201, Folder 15)
    - Walcott, Jersey Joe -- World champion (Box 201, Folder 8)
    - Waldorf, Lynn "Pappy" (Box 201, Folder 9)
    - Walker -- Miscellaneous (Box 202, Folder 1-3)
    - Walker, Cheryl -- Actress (Box 202, Folder 4)
    - Walker, Helen (Box 202, Folder 5)
    - Walker, Robert -- Actor -- Died August 28, 1951 (Box 202, Folder 6)
    - Walker, Walton H., General -- And Wife (Box 202, Folder 7)
    - Wallace -- Miscellaneous (Box 202, Folder 8)
    - Wallace, Henry (Box 202, Folder 9)
    - Wallard, Lee (Box 202, Folder 10)
    - Walsh -- Miscellaneous (Box 202, Folder 11)
    - Walter-Walters -- Miscellaneous (Box 202, Folder 12)
    - Wam-War (Box 202, Folder 13)
    - Wanger, Walter (Box 202, Folder 14)
    - Ward -- Miscellaneous (Box 202, Folder 15)
    - Ward, Angus (Box 202, Folder 16)
    - Warner -- Miscellaneous (Box 202, Folder 17)
    - Warren -- Miscellaneous (Box 203, Folder 1)
    - Warren, Earl, Governor (Box 203, Folder 2-10)
    - Warrick -- Miscellaneous (Box 203, Folder 11)
    - Was-Waz (Box 203, Folder 12-13)
    - Washburn -- Miscellaneous (Box 203, Folder 14)
    - Washburn, Carole -- Rose Queen of 1961 (Box 203, Folder 15)
    - Washington -- Miscellaneous (Box 203, Folder 16)
    - Washington, George (Box 203, Folder 17)
    - Waters -- Miscellaneous (Box 204, Folder 1)
    - Watkins -- Miscellaneous (Box 204, Folder 2)
    - Watson -- Miscellaneous (Box 204, Folder 3)
    - Watts -- Miscellaneous (Box 204, Folder 4)
    - Wayne -- Miscellaneous (Box 204, Folder 5)
    - Wayne, David -- Actor (Box 204, Folder 6)
    - Wea- (Box 204, Folder 7-14)
    - Weaver -- Miscellaneous (Box 204, Folder 15)
    - Webb -- A to Z (Box 204, Folder 16)
    - Wedemeyer, Albert C., General (Box 205, Folder 1)
    - Weinberger, Peter, Mr. and Mrs. Morris, and Beatrice -- Kidnap Case (Box 205, Folder 2)
    - Weiss -- Miscellaneous (Box 205, Folder 3)
    - Weissmuller -- Miscellaneous (Box 205, Folder 4)
    - Weissmuller, Johnny (Box 205, Folder 5)
    - Weizmann, Chaim, Doctor (Box 205, Folder 6)
    - Wel-Wez (Box 205, Folder 7-12)
    - Welles -- Miscellaneous (Box 206, Folder 1)
    - Wells -- Miscellaneous (Box 206, Folder 2)
    - Wha-Whz (Box 205, Folder 13-16)
    - Wheeler -- Miscellaneous (Box 206, Folder 3)
    - Wherry -- Kenneth S. (Box 206, Folder 4)
    - White, A-Z (Box 206, Folder 5)
    - White, Margaret (Box 206, Folder 6)
    - Whitfield, Mal -- Track (Box 207, Folder 1)
    - Whitney, A-Z (Box 207, Folder 2)
    - Wi-Wim (Box 207, Folder 3-8)
    - Widmark, Richard (Box 207, Folder 9)
    - Wieck, Dorothy -- Actress (Box 207, Folder 10)
    - Wiedemann -- Miscellaneous (Box 207, Folder 11)
    - Wilcoxon, Henry (Box 207, Folder 12)
    - Wilde -- Miscellaneous (Box 207, Folder 13)
    - Wilde, Cornel -- Actor (Box 207, Folder 14)
    - Wiley -- Miscellaneous (Box 207, Folder 15)
    - Wilkinson -- Miscellaneous (Box 207, Folder 16)
    - Williams -- Miscellaneous (Box 208, Folder 1)
    - Williams, Ben -- Mr. and Mrs. (Box 208, Folder 2)
    - Williams, Bill -- And Wife (Box 208, Folder 3)
    - Williams, Ester -- Actress (Box 208, Folder 4)
    - Williams, Eugene, Assistant Attorney General (Box 208, Folder 5)
    - Williams, Kay -- Mrs. Adolph Spreckles (Box 208, Folder 6)
    - Williams, Mona (Box 208, Folder 7)
    - Williams, Ted (Box 208, Folder 8)
    - Williamson -- Miscellaneous (Box 208, Folder 9)
    - Wilson -- Miscellaneous (Box 208, Folder 11)
    - Wilson -- Miscellaneous (Box 209, Folder 1)
    - Wilson, Charles E. -- General Electric -- Mobilization Director (Box 209, Folder 2)
    - Wilson, Marie (Box 208, Folder 10)
    - Win-Wj (Box 209, Folder 3)
    - Winant -- Miscellaneous (Box 211, Folder 1)
    - Windsor -- Duke and Duchess (Box 210, Folder 2)
    - Windsor -- Miscellaneous (Box 210, Folder 1)
    - Winter-Winters -- Miscellaneous (Box 210, Folder 3)
    - Winters, Shirley (Box 210, Folder 4)
    - Withers, Jane (Box 210, Folder 5)
    - Wl-Wr (Box 211, Folder 6-13)
    - Wong -- Miscellaneous (Box 211, Folder 2)
    - Wood-Woods -- Miscellaneous (Box 211, Folder 3)
    - Wood, Gertrude -- Rose Queen of 1958 (Box 211, Folder 4)
    - Wood, Natalie (Box 211, Folder 5)
    - Woodling, Gene (Box 212, Folder 1)
    - Woodward, Joanne -- Alone (Box 212, Folder 3)
    - Woodward, Joanne -- Groups (Box 212, Folder 4)
    - Wright -- Miscellaneous (Box 212, Folder 2)
    - Wright, Cobina -- Junior and Senior (Box 212, Folder 5)
    - Wright, Orville (Box 212, Folder 6)
    - Wright, Teresa (Box 212, Folder 7)
    - Ws-Wz (Box 212, Folder 8)
    - Wyman, Jane -- Actress -- Alone (Box 213, Folder 1 - 3)
    - Wyman, Jane -- Actress -- Groups (Box 213, Folder 4 - 6)
    - Wynn -- Miscellaneous (Box 213, Folder 7)
    - Wynn, Ed (Box 213, Folder 8)
    - Wynn, Keenan -- Actor (Box 213, Folder 9)
    - Wynter, Dana -- Actress (Box 213, Folder 10)
    - Wynyard, Diana -- Actress (Box 213, Folder 11)
  - X, Y, Z
    - X-Yz (Box 214, Folder 1)
    - Yamashita -- Miscellaneous (Box 214, Folder 2)
    - Yates -- Miscellaneous (Box 214, Folder 3)
    - Ybarbo -- Miscellaneous (Box 214, Folder 4)
    - Yeager -- Miscellaneous (Box 214, Folder 5)
    - Yorty, Samuel W., Mayor (Box 214, Folder 6)
    - Yoshida, Shigeru (Box 214, Folder 7)
    - Young, A-M (Box 214, Folder 8-10)
    - Young, Alan (Box 214, Folder 11)
    - Young, E. Merl (Box 215, Folder 2)
    - Young, Elizabeth (Box 215, Folder 1)
    - Young, Loretta -- Actress (Box 215, Folder 3)
    - Young, N-Z (Box 215, Folder 4)
    - Young, Robert -- Actor (Box 215, Folder 5)
    - Youngdahl, Luther (Box 215, Folder 6)
    - Yugoslavia -- Royalty (Box 215, Folder 7)
    - Za-Zm (Box 216, Folder 1-6)
    - Zaharias, Mildred "Babe" (Box 216, Folder 7)
    - Zale, Tony -- Boxer (Box 216, Folder 8)
    - Zanuck -- Miscellaneous (Box 216, Folder 9)
    - Zender, Gladys -- Miss Universe of 1958 (Box 216, Folder 10)
    - Zilbauer, Anthony J. -- Slayer (Box 216, Folder 11)
- Oversize Subject Files
  - A
    - Accidents -- Auto -- California and Local (Box 228, Folder 6)
    - Accidents -- Auto -- Local -- 1951-1952 (Box 227, Folder 4)
    - Accidents -- Auto -- Local -- 1953-1954 (Box 217, Folder 1)
    - Accidents -- Auto -- Local -- 1955 (Box 217, Folder 2)
    - Accidents -- Auto -- Local -- 1956 (Box 217, Folder 3)
    - Accidents -- Auto -- Local -- 1957 (Box 217, Folder 4)
    - Accidents -- Auto -- Local and state --1948 (Box 227, Folder 2)
    - Accidents -- Auto -- Local and state -- 1949 (Box 227, Folder 3)
    - Accidents -- Auto -- Local and state -- 1958 (Box 218, Folder 1)
    - Accidents -- Auto -- Local and state -- 1959-1961 (Box 218, Folder 2)
    - Accidents -- Auto -- U.S (Box 228, Folder 3-5)
    - Accidents -- Auto Racing (Box 218, Folder 3)
    - Accidents -- Aviation -- Dirigible (Box 222, Folder 2)
    - Accidents -- Aviation -- Eastern Airlines (Box 222, Folder 3)
    - Accidents -- Aviation -- Elizabeth, New Jersey (Box 222, Folder 4)
    - Accidents -- Aviation -- Empire State Building -- July 28, 1945 (Box 222, Folder 5)
    - Accidents -- Aviation -- Foreign (Box 220, Folder 2)
    - Accidents -- Aviation -- Local and State -- 1945-1948 (Box 220, Folder 3)
    - Accidents -- Aviation -- Local and State -- 1951-1952 (Box 220, Folder 4)
    - Accidents -- Aviation -- Local and State -- 1953 (Box 220, Folder 5)
    - Accidents -- Aviation -- Local and State -- 1955-1957 (Box 221, Folder 1)
    - Accidents -- Aviation -- Miscellaneous (Box 219, Folder 9)
    - Accidents -- Aviation -- Miscellaneous (Box 220, Folder 1)
    - Accidents -- Aviation -- Norwalk -- February 1, 1958 (Box 222, Folder 6)
    - Accidents -- Aviation -- San Fernando Valley -- Pacoima Jr. High School -- January 31, 1957 (Box 222, Folder 7)
    - Accidents -- Aviation -- U.S. -- 1945-1947 (Box 221, Folder 2-3)
    - Accidents -- Aviation -- U.S. -- Brooklyn-Staten Island (Box 222, Folder 1)
    - Accidents -- Aviation -- U.S. Air Force, U.S. Navy, U.S. Marines (Box 222, Folder 8)
    - Accidents -- Aviation -- U.S. Marines, U.S. Army, U.S. Navy -- 1951 (Box 223, Folder 1)
    - Accidents -- Buildings Collapse -- Structures, Bridges, Scaffolds, Grandstands (Box 225, Folder 2)
    - Accidents -- Cave-ins (Box 225, Folder 3)
    - Accidents -- Drowning (Box 225, Folder 4)
    - Accidents -- Explosions -- Local (Box 227, Folder 1)
    - Accidents -- Explosions -- Miscellaneous (Box 226, Folder 1)
    - Accidents -- Explosions -- Port Chicago Blast -- July 17, 1945 (Box 226, Folder 3)
    - Accidents -- Explosions -- Ships (Box 226, Folder 4)
    - Accidents -- Explosions -- Texas City (Box 226, Folder 5)
    - Accidents -- Explosions -- U.S. (Box 226, Folder 2)
    - Accidents -- Falls (Box 226, Folder 6)
    - Accidents -- Landslides (Box 226, Folder 7)
    - Accidents -- Landslides -- Pacific Coast Highway Area (Box 229, Folder 1)
    - Accidents -- Mines (Box 229, Folder 2)
    - Accidents -- Miscellaneous (Box 219, Folder 1-8)
    - Accidents -- Miscellaneous (Box 225, Folder 1)
    - Accidents -- Missiles and rockets -- Miscellaneous (Box 229, Folder 3)
    - Accidents -- Railroad -- 1945-1947 (Box 223, Folder 2)
    - Accidents -- Railroad -- 1945 (Box 223, Folder 3)
    - Accidents -- Railroad -- 1946 (Box 223, Folder 4)
    - Accidents -- Railroad -- 1947 (Box 223, Folder 5)
    - Accidents -- Railroad -- 1948-1949 (Box 223, Folder 6)
    - Accidents -- Railroad -- Long Island -- 1950 (Box 224, Folder 2)
    - Accidents -- Railroad -- Miscellaneous -- 1950 (Box 224, Folder 1)
    - Accidents -- Railroad -- 1951-1952 (Box 224, Folder 3)
    - Accidents -- Railroad -- 1953 (Box 224, Folder 5)
    - Accidents -- Railroad -- 1953-1954 (Box 235, Folder 1)
    - Accidents -- Railroad -- 1960 (Box 235, Folder 3)
    - Accidents -- Railroad -- Pennsylvania -- January 1951 (Box 224, Folder 4)
    - Accidents -- Railroad and Jet plane -- El Toro, California, November 1958 (Box 235, Folder 2)
    - Accidents -- Shipping -- 1946-1949 (Box 229, Folder 4-10)
    - Accidents -- Shipping -- 1950 (Box 229, Folder 11-17)
    - Accidents -- Shipping -- September 1, 1951 (Box 229, Folder 18)
    - Accidents -- Shipping -- July 1960 (Box 229, Folder 19)
    - Accidents -- Streets -- Railway (Box 228, Folder 1)
    - Accidents -- Streets -- Truck and Bus (Box 228, Folder 2)
    - Aa-Az -- Miscellaneous (Box 230, Folder 1)
    - Acrobats (Box 230, Folder 2)
    - Aleutian Islands (Box 230, Folder 3)
    - Algeria (Box 230, Folder 4)
    - Aliens (Box 230, Folder 5)
    - American Legion (Box 230, Folder 6)
    - American Legion Convention -- 1950 (Box 230, Folder 7)
    - American Legion Convention -- Los Angeles -- 1956 (Box 231, Folder 1)
    - Americanism (Box 231, Folder 2)
    - Archaeology -- Miscellaneous (Box 231, Folder 3)
    - Argentine (Box 231, Folder 4)
    - Armistice Day (Box 231, Folder 5)
    - Art (Box 231, Folder 6)
    - Art -- Cartoon (Box 232, Folder 1)
    - Art -- Festivals -- Exhibits -- Miscellaneous (Box 232, Folder 2)
    - Art -- Institutes -- Los Angeles County (Box 232, Folder 3)
    - Art -- Paintings (Box 232, Folder 4)
    - Associations -- A -- Miscellaneous (Box 232, Folder 5)
    - Associations -- Alumnae -- Miscellaneous (Box 232, Folder 6)
    - Associations -- Assistance league (Box 232, Folder 7)
    - Associations -- B (Box 233, Folder 1)
    - Associations -- C-G (Box 233, Folder 2)
    - Associations -- Catholic (Box 233, Folder 3)
    - Associations -- Children (Box 233, Folder 4)
    - Associations -- H-L (Box 233, Folder 5)
    - Associations -- Hospital (Box 233, Folder 6)
    - Associations -- M-R (Box 233, Folder 7)
    - Associations -- Oakmont league (Box 233, Folder 8)
    - Associations -- Parent-teachers (Box 233, Folder 9)
    - Associations -- S (Box 233, Folder 10)
    - Associations -- Shriners -- 1950 (Box 234, Folder 1)
    - Associations -- Shrine -- Convention -- 1950 (Box 234, Folder 2)
    - Associations -- Society For the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (Box 234, Folder 3)
    - Associations -- Sororities (Box 234, Folder 4)
    - Associations -- T-Z (Box 234, Folder 5)
    - Astronomy -- Miscellaneous (Box 234, Folder 6)
    - Atomic energy -- Miscellaneous -- 1947 and Before (Box 235, Folder 4)
    - Atomic energy -- Miscellaneous -- 1948-1949 (Box 235, Folder 5)
    - Atomic energy -- Miscellaneous -- 1950-1952 -- Includes pictures of Inside of Bomb (Box 235, Folder 6)
    - Atomic energy -- Miscellaneous -- 1953-1956 (Box 235, Folder 7)
    - Atomic energy -- Defense (Box 235, Folder 8)
    - Atomic energy -- Hydrogen Bomb (Box 235, Folder 9)
    - Atomic energy -- Maps (Box 236, Folder 1)
    - Atomic energy -- Nagasaki and Hiroshima (Box 236, Folder 2)
    - Atomic energy -- Plants and Laboratories (Box 236, Folder 3)
    - Atomic energy -- Radioactivity (Box 236, Folder 4)
    - Atomic energy -- Reactors (Box 236, Folder 5)
    - Atomic energy -- Test -- Atomic artillery (Box 236, Folder 6)
    - Atomic energy -- Bikini test number 1 -- Before Bombing (Box 236, Folder 7)
    - Atomic energy -- Bikini test number 1 -- Actual Explosion -- July 1, 1946 (Box 236, Folder 8)
    - Atomic energy -- Bikini test number 1 -- After Bombing -- July 1, 1946 (Box 236, Folder 9)
    - Atomic energy -- Bikini test number 2 -- Preparations -- July 25, 1946 (Box 236, Folder 10)
    - Atomic energy -- Bikini test number 2 -- Explosion -- July 25, 1946 (Box 236, Folder 11)
    - Atomic energy -- Bikini test number 2 -- After Bombing -- July 25, 1946 (Box 236, Folder 12)
    - Atomic energy -- Tests -- Nevada -- January-March 1951 (Box 236, Folder 13)
    - Atomic energy -- Tests -- Nevada -- April to October -- 1951 (Box 237, Folder 1)
    - Atomic energy -- Tests -- Nevada -- November to December 1951 (Box 237, Folder 2)
    - Atomic energy -- Tests -- Nevada -- January to April 1952 (Box 237, Folder 3)
    - Atomic energy -- Tests -- Nevada -- May to December 1952 (Box 237, Folder 4)
    - Atomic energy -- Tests -- Nevada -- January to March 1953 (Box 237, Folder 5)
    - Atomic energy -- Tests -- Nevada -- April to December 1953 (Box 237, Folder 6)
    - Atomic energy -- Tests -- Nevada -- January to June 1955 (Box 237, Folder 7)
    - Atomic energy -- Tests -- Nevada --1955 (Box 237, Folder 8)
    - Atomic energy -- Tests -- New Mexico (Box 237, Folder 9)
    - Atomic energy -- Weapons -- Includes "Big Bertha" (Box 237, Folder 10)
    - Autos -- Miscellaneous (Box 238, Folder 1)
    - Autos -- Companies -- Miscellaneous (Box 238, Folder 2)
    - Autos -- Old -- Miscellaneous (Box 238, Folder 3)
    - Autos -- Racing -- Miscellaneous (Box 238, Folder 4)
    - Autos -- Racing -- Indianapolis -- Miscellaneous (Box 238, Folder 5)
    - Autos -- Racing -- Pomona Course (Box 238, Folder 6)
    - Autos -- Traffic -- Jams (Box 238, Folder 7)
    - Autos -- Traffic -- Scramble System (Box 238, Folder 8)
    - Aviation -- Miscellaneous -- Envelope 1 (Box 238, Folder 9)
    - Aviation -- Miscellaneous -- Envelope 2 (Box 238, Folder 10)
    - Aviation -- Dirigible (Box 238, Folder 11)
    - Aviation -- Drone Planes (Box 239, Folder 1)
    - Aviation -- Factories (Box 239, Folder 2)
    - Aviation -- Fields (Box 239, Folder 3-4)
    - Aviation -- Fields -- International Airport (Box 239, Folder 5)
    - Aviation -- Flights (Box 239, Folder 6-8)
    - Aviation -- Gliders (Box 239, Folder 9)
    - Aviation -- Helicopters (Box 239, Folder 10)
    - Aviation -- Jets (Box 240, Folder 1)
    - Aviation -- Jets -- Envelope 2 (Box 240, Folder 2)
    - Aviation -- Jets -- Parachutes (Box 240, Folder 3)
    - Aviation -- Races (Box 240, Folder 4)
    - Aviation -- Refueling in Mid-air (Box 240, Folder 5)
    - Aviation -- Rockets (Box 240, Folder 6)
    - Aviation -- Foreign -- England (Box 240, Folder 8)
    - Aviation -- Foreign -- Germany (Box 240, Folder 9)
    - Aviation -- Foreign -- Miscellaneous (Box 240, Folder 7)
    - Aviation -- Foreign -- Russia (Box 241, Folder 1)
    - Aviation -- Makes -- Miscellaneous (Box 241, Folder 2)
    - Aviation -- Makes -- Douglas (Box 241, Folder 3)
    - Aviation -- Makes -- Hughes (Box 241, Folder 4)
    - Aviation -- Makes -- Lockheed (Box 241, Folder 5)
    - Aviation -- Makes -- Northrup (Box 241, Folder 6)
    - Aviation -- U.S. Air Force -- Bombers -- B19 (Box 242, Folder 2)
    - Aviation -- U.S. Air Force -- Bombers -- B36 (Box 242, Folder 3)
    - Aviation -- U.S. Air Force -- Bombers -- B47 (Box 242, Folder 4)
    - Aviation -- U.S. Air Force -- Bombers -- Miscellaneous (Box 242, Folder 1)
    - Aviation -- U.S. Air Force -- Fields (Box 242, Folder 5)
    - Aviation -- U.S. Air Force -- Miscellaneous (Box 241, Folder 7)
    - Aviation -- U.S. Air Force -- Production (Box 243, Folder 1)
    - Aviation -- U.S. Air Force -- Rescues (Box 243, Folder 2)
    - Aviation -- U.S. Army -- Bombers -- B17 Flying Fortress (Box 242, Folder 6)
    - Aviation -- U.S. Army -- Bombers -- B29 Super Fortress (Box 242, Folder 7)
    - Aviation -- U.S. Army -- Crews (Box 242, Folder 8)
    - Aviation -- U.S. Army -- Gliders (Box 242, Folder 9)
    - Aviation -- U.S. Army -- Overseas scenes (Box 242, Folder 10)
    - Aviation -- U.S. Army -- Paratroops (Box 242, Folder 11)
    - Aviation -- U.S. Army -- Training (Box 243, Folder 3)
    - Aviation -- U.S. Air Force -- Transports (Box 243, Folder 4)
    - Aviation -- U.S. Marines (Box 243, Folder 5)
    - Aviation -- U.S. Navy (Box 243, Folder 6)
    - Australia (Box 243, Folder 7)
    - Azores (Box 243, Folder 8)
  - B
    - Ba-Bz (Box 243, Folder 9)
    - Babies (Box 244, Folder 1-10)
    - Balls (Box 244, Folder 11)
    - Bands -- Musical (Box 244, Folder 12)
    - Banks (Box 244, Folder 13)
    - Baseball -- Miscellaneous teams -- High School, University, Sandlot, Junior, etc. (Box 250, Folder 1)
    - Baseball -- Boston Red Sox (Box 250, Folder 2)
    - Baseball -- Brooklyn Dodgers (Box 250, Folder 3)
    - Baseball -- Brooklyn Dodgers to Los Angeles (Box 250, Folder 4)
    - Baseball -- Chicago Cubs (Box 250, Folder 5)
    - Baseball -- Chicago White Sox (Box 250, Folder 6)
    - Baseball -- Cleveland Indians (Box 250, Folder 7)
    - Baseball -- Coast league -- Hollywood stars (Box 251, Folder 1-8)
    - Baseball -- Coast league -- Los Angeles Angels (Box 255, Folder 1-8)
    - Baseball -- Coast league -- Miscellaneous (Box 252, Folder 1)
    - Baseball -- Fans (Box 252, Folder 2)
    - Baseball -- Fielding plays -- Action Shots (Box 252, Folder 3)
    - Baseball -- Hollywood stars --1954 (Box 251, Folder 9)
    - Baseball -- Hollywood stars -- 1955 (Box 251, Folder 10)
    - Baseball -- Los Angeles Angels (Box 255, Folder 13)
    - Baseball -- Los Angeles Angels --1954-1956 (Box 255, Folder 9 - 12)
    - Baseball -- Los Angeles Dodgers -- First Day (Box 255, Folder 15)
    - Baseball -- Los Angeles Dodgers -- Miscellaneous (Box 254, Folder 1)
    - Baseball -- Los Angeles Dodgers -- 1958 (Box 254, Folder 2)